<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ESRI_ItemInformation Culture='en-US'>
<name>bf8db57ee6e0420c8ecce3c6395aceeb</name>
<guid>BECF9B52-DC9F-476C-A04A-EFB05360D8BE</guid>
<catalogpath></catalogpath>
<snippet></snippet>
<description>This dataset represents USDA Forest Service fire perimeters 10+ acres
and California Dept of Forestry fire perimeters 300+ acres occurring
from the year 1950 to 2007. The geographic extent of the fires includes
the State of California, Region 5 Forests (some R5 Forests have
boundaries falling outside CA) and the Toiyabe National Forest in Region
4.  Some fires before 1950 are also included. Fires are compiled from
both historic and recently mapped records. This layer contains records
up to and including fires from 2018.&lt;div&gt;&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;&lt;div&gt;Fire18_1 was released May 1st, 2019. 413 wildfires from the 2018 fire season were added to the database. There are two fires on BIA managed land that do not have 3 letter code identifiers and thus &quot;Unit&quot; was left blank. A hand drawn perimeter of the 1990 San Juan Canyon fire in BEU was submitted by a fire fighter who worked on the fire. The perimeter of the Thomas fire of 2017 was replaced this year by one collected by SBC that is based on someone walking some parts of the perimeter for better accuracy.&lt;br/&gt;&lt;/div&gt;

This dataset was uploaded to Data Basin and is available with additional information at: /datasets/bf8db57ee6e0420c8ecce3c6395aceeb</description>
<summary></summary>
<title>bf8db57ee6e0420c8ecce3c6395aceeb</title>
<tags></tags>
<type>Layer Package</type>
<typekeywords>
<typekeyword>Shapefile Feature Class</typekeyword>
<typekeyword>Layer Package</typekeyword>
<typekeyword>Data</typekeyword>
<typekeyword>ArcMap</typekeyword>
<typekeyword>ArcGlobe</typekeyword>
<typekeyword>ArcGIS Explorer</typekeyword>
<typekeyword>lpk</typekeyword>
</typekeywords>
<thumbnail>thumbnail/thumbnail.png</thumbnail>
<documentation></documentation>
<url></url>
<datalastmodifiedtime></datalastmodifiedtime>
<extent>
<xmin>-124.536479491444</xmin>
<ymin>32.4324403786401</ymin>
<xmax>-113.684420906402</xmax>
<ymax>42.6846091032515</ymax>
</extent>
<spatialreference>NAD_1983_California_Teale_Albers</spatialreference>
<accessinformation>CDF,USFS,BLM,NPS.</accessinformation>
<licenseinfo></licenseinfo>
</ESRI_ItemInformation>
